And so I want us to go to the book of
Matthew chapter number 16.
And please um
I was asking the Lord, how will I teach
this thing? And he reminded me of
Ukraine.
He said when war broke out, suddenly
there was a crash program to train
civilians on how to become soldiers.
There was no time for the 9-month season
to stay in the barracks. But in less
than 2 weeks, I even saw the Miss
Ukraine with a gun. In less than 2
weeks, even models were warriors.
And so I believe the same grace is
available tonight
that we can recruit slay queens to
warriors because the time time is
urgent.
Matthew 16 and verse 13.
I'm a Bible teacher, and so if I don't
teach like your pastor, please
this is me.
When Jesus came into the region of
Caesarea Philippi, he asked his
disciples saying, "Who do men say that
I,
the Son of Man, am?"
Two things I want to highlight from
there.
Why was this region? Why is it that it
is in this region that he decided to
project that question?
The point here was in this area of
Caesarea Philippi,
it was an area dominated by stones that
were engraved with names of different
deities.
So as they were walking, they just come
across this area, but this area was
unique because it was surrounded by
stones
that were engraved with the names of
different deities.
And we know that Jesus is the rock of
ages. So he entered into a region of
rocks, and he needed them to begin to
[music] identify which rock is which.
SO AS A GEOLOGIST, WE ARE ABOUT TO HAVE
A conversation on rocks.
That's my background. I studied about
rocks. So this is a very geological
topic.
>> [gasps]
>> If I was to CALL THIS SESSION, I'LL call
it geology, spiritual geology.
Hallelujah. And so at this TIME HE MUST
ASK THEM, "WHO WHO DO MEN say that I,
the Son of Man, am?" THIS IS VERY
POWERFUL BECAUSE EVERY SON OF God is
supposed to be a son of man.
I KNOW THE DOCTRINE OF FATHERHOOD has
been taught by the wrong office.
NOW LET ME EXPLAIN. THERE ARE TEACHINGS
THAT ARE SPECIFIC TO CERTAIN OFFICES.
SO WHEN WE BEGIN to teach from certain
offices, we might teach men error.
A VERY GOOD EXAMPLE, YOU CAN ONLY
UNDERSTAND THE PROPHETIC when it is
TAUGHT BY GENUINE PROPHETS.
OTHERWISE, AS AN EVANGELIST, YOU MAY NOT
HAVE THE GRACE TO EXPOUND ON THE
PROPHETIC
BECAUSE YOU YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND [music]
THE OFFICE AND YOU DON'T operate from
it.
NOW WHEN IT COMES TO THE DOCTRINE OF
FATHERHOOD AND SONSHIP, IT CAN ONLY BE
TAUGHT BY APOSTLES.
NOW THE PROBLEM IS THE CHURCH HAS
EMBRACED APOSTOLIC BOOKS, BUT THEY HAVE
NOT EMBRACED APOSTOLIC SPIRIT.
SO WHATEVER WE ARE RUNNING IS NOT A
SYSTEM OF FATHERS AND SONS, WE ARE
RUNNING A SYSTEM OF MASTERS AND
SERVANTS.
BECAUSE THE LANGUAGE OF SON SONSHIP AND
FATHERHOOD IS NOT A LANGUAGE OF
SUPERIORITY AND INFERIORITY, IS A
LANGUAGE OF FELLOWSHIP AND FAMILY.
BECAUSE GOD NEVER LEFT A DENOMINATION.
THE LORD LEFT A CONGREGATION THAT WAS
MEANT TO MATURE AND BECOME A FELLOWSHIP
AND A FAMILY. BUT WHEN DENOMINATIONS
CAME ON BOARD, WE LOST THE SPIRIT OF
FAMILY. SO THE APOSTOLIC TEMPLATE IS NOT
PER SE [music] DENOMINATIONAL, IS
RELATIONAL.
SO I DON'T BECOME A FATHER
UH-OH, SIMPLY BECAUSE I'M DRIVING A V8
AND ALL THE PEOPLE IN THE CHURCH ARE
WALKING. THAT DOES NOT MAKE ME A FATHER.
I BECOME A FATHER BECAUSE THERE ARE MEN
I HAVE BIRTHED IN THE SPIRIT AND I HAVE
RAISED THEM IN THE DOCTRINE AND IN THE
WORD OF GOD.
BUT TODAY WE HAVE MANY ADOPTED SONS AND
VERY FEW SONS WE HAVE DELIVERED BECAUSE
PEOPLE move from one house TO ANOTHER.
AND ONE OF THE RISKS OF MOVING FROM ONE
HOUSE TO ANOTHER IS THAT WHEN YOU KEEP
ON TRANSPLANTING A TREE, THE ROOTS
become weak and it withers. LOOK AT
PEOPLE WHO DON'T STAY IN A CERTAIN
MINISTRY FOR LONG, THEY DON'T GROW.
PERPETUALLY, THEY are always in the SAME
LEVEL.
AND FATHERHOOD IS NOT ABOUT RESULTS, IS
ABOUT GRACE.
BECAUSE A MAN CAN BE RUNNING A CHURCH OF
30 MEMBERS, BUT THOSE 30 MEMBERS ARE 30
APOSTLES. IF YOU WERE TO WEIGH THE
MINISTRY OF JESUS BY NUMBERS, YOU WOULD
HAVE FAILED.
IT IS IT WAS ONLY DURING BREAD MEETINGS
THAT 5,000 CAME.
BUT THE GENUINE MEETING WAS AMONG 12
APOSTLES THAT COULD HANDLE A GLOBAL
MINISTRY. SO FATHERHOOD IS ABOUT GRACE.
AND NO MATTER WHO YOU ARE, EVEN WHEN YOU
meet Jesus in person, Jesus will still
refer you to a man, ask Paul.
YOU KNOW THERE ARE PEOPLE YOUNG PEOPLE
SOMETIMES THINK BECAUSE I'M HAVING
ENCOUNTERS THAT MY MY SENIOR HAS NOT
HAD, THEN I THINK I NEED A MAN WHO'S
HAVING ENCOUNTERS in my level. I
listened to a man who said, "I was
reading Isaiah and Isaiah showed up IN
MY BEDROOM. I DECIDED TO READ JEREMIAH,
HE didn't show up." SO I WAS WONDERING,
WHAT IS NOT HAPPENING? HOW COMES ISAIAH
IS SHOWING UP? AND I REALIZED IT'S NOT
IN THE ENCOUNTERS, IT is in the grace.
AND AND GRACE IS CARRIED BY MEN, SO YOU
MUST UNDERSTAND THAT THERE IS A MAN THAT
CARRIES THE GRACE. IF YOU ENCOUNTER THE
MAN, YOU MIGHT MISS THE GRACE.
It is a man that carries the grace.
Do you know in reality Elijah
was younger than Elisha.
But Elisha submitted under Elijah. He
was not submitting under the man, he was
submitting under the grace.
And And this is what I've discovered,
especially in this age of social media
culture, one of the dominant culture is
cancellation culture.
AND THERE ARE MANY GRACES WE ARE GOING
TO DISBURSE.
Like I saw Let me say this because I saw
it. I saw the man of God being given a
sword somewhere in Ghana.
AND EVERYBODY NOW FORMULATED
A THEORY
and even when we did the Rama first, we
were called devil worshipers. Even
though I'm wearing black, people say I
came to recruit you now.
AND THAT'S WHY WE MUST BE SENSITIVE OF
WHAT WE HEAR BECAUSE THERE ARE GRACES WE
WERE MEANT TO BENEFIT FROM, BUT SOMEONE
JUST CAME AND SAID, "THE TOP TOP 10
DEVIL WORSHIPERS IN KENYA, NUMBER FIVE
WILL SURPRISE YOU."
AND THEN YOU ARE THERE ONLINE SAYING,
"THAT'S WHY I DON'T GO TO [music]
CHURCH." AND THAT'S WHY GRACES DON'T
WORK FOR YOU.
SO THE DEVIL MUST BEGIN TO INTRODUCE
CERTAIN BRANDS AND SOMETIMES INTRODUCE
[music]
WRONG REPRESENTATIONS
TO MAKE it look like this is the church.
I WANT TO ASSURE YOU, NO MAN CHOSE THE
GRACE THEY CARRY.
THERE WAS NO APPLICATION IN HEAVEN THAT
FATHER, MAKE ME AN APOSTLE, MAKE ME A
PROPHET. THE BIBLE SAYS HE GIVE GIFTS TO
men and he gives to whoever he wishes.
THAT'S WHY SOMETIMES I'M EVEN sensitive
when when a backslidden preacher is
abandoned because you may not know the
secret prayers of David, but you are
aware of the public scandal OF [music]
DAVID.
THAT DAVID HAS SLEPT WITH BATHSHEBA, IT
IS ON ALL BLOGGERS, BUT THE BLOGGERS
NEVER CAME WHEN HE SAID, "LORD, one
thing I desire. Lord, I know you do not
desire bulls and all these things, but
one thing I know is that let me fall in
your hand BECAUSE A BROKEN HEART AND A
CONTRITE SPIRIT, THAT ONE YOU CANNOT
REJECT." THE BLOGGERS WERE NOT THERE.
WHEN HE WAS TELLING THE LORD, "YOU CAN
TAKE AWAY MY THRONE, BUT DON'T TAKE AWAY
THE HOLY GHOST," THE BLOGGERS WERE NOT
THERE. BUT FOR 10 YEARS, YOU KEEP ON
SEEING DAVID AS A WOMANIZER. Yet he is a
carrier of grace.
Am I SPEAKING TO ANYONE? WHY DO YOU KNOW
WHY I'M SAYING THAT? BECAUSE YOU WHO IS
LISTENING to me, one day you'll be the
one standing here and you have a
history.
In Kampala, when you bump INTO A GIRL,
MADAM KIBAO. AND THEN NOW WE LOOK AT YOU
AND WE PULL YOUR FILE AND YOU'RE LIKE,
"BOSS, WHO ARE YOU AND IS THAT YOUR
APOSTLE?" LISTEN, GOD CAN CHANGE A
MURDERER TO BE an apostle.
GOD CAN CHANGE A MAN ON A MISSION TO
PERSECUTE A CHURCH, BUT EVEN AFTER THAT,
CAN I GO FURTHER?
I'M NOT ON MY message yet. I'm just
dealing with this one verse
of Son OF MAN. IF JESUS WAS A SON OF
MAN,
SO PAUL ENCOUNTERS JESUS. AND LET ME
TELL YOU, HE NEVER ENCOUNTERED THE JESUS
THAT Peter encountered.
Okay, it's the same Jesus
because we have THE MAN JESUS, THE
CRUCIFIED JESUS, THE RESURRECTED JESUS,
and the glorified Jesus.
There is the man Jesus born of Mary,
taken to the temple for CIRCUMCISION
THAT A PRIEST can circumcise God.
Hey.
AND HE'S INTERACTING WITH THE BLOOD THAT
THE BLOOD DOES NOT AFFECT HIM. BECAUSE
EVEN IN THE LEVEL OF THE MAN JESUS, HE
DOESN'T KNOW.
THE ANGELS ARE COMING AND THEY ARE
CRYING AND THEY ARE SAYING, "WHERE IS
HE, THE KING?" HALLELUJAH. SAYING,
"HALLELUJAH. HALLELUJAH." AND THEY ARE
SAYING, "BEHOLD, THE KING HAS BEEN BORN
IN A MANGER."
BUT ACCORDING TO REALITY, HE'S A child
wrapped up, SADDLED UP.
THE WISE MEN ARE NOT LOOKING FOR A
CHILD. THE STAR NEVER REVEALED A CHILD.
THE STAR REVEALED A KING WE CAN WORSHIP.
Those are witches OF BABYLON.
THOSE ARE WITCHES WHO USED TO ADVISE
NEBUCHADNEZZAR.
BECAUSE NEBUCHADNEZZAR NEEDED THEM FOR
THE WISDOM. BUT NOW, THESE WITCHES HAVE
SEEN A STAR AND THEY HAVE REALIZED THERE
IS ANOTHER KING WE CANNOT ADVISE. WE CAN
ONLY WORSHIP.
AND THEY ARE LOOKING FOR HIM AND THEY
COME TO HEROD AND THEY BYPASS HEROD.
HEROD IS SEEKING THEIR ADVICE, BUT THEY
ARE LOOKING FOR A king to worship. AND
THEY UNDERSTAND THE GRAMMAR OF WORSHIP
IS NOT MELODY. [music] THE GRAMMAR OF
WORSHIP IS SACRIFICE.
PASTOR, WE HAVE GONE FOR PRAISE AND
WORSHIP.
IT'S NOT SONGS.
THE THEOLOGICAL GRAMMAR OF WORSHIP IS
SACRIFICE. SACRIFICE IS WHAT CONFIRMED
WHO YOU ENDORSE AS GOD.
ALTARS WERE RAISED FOR BAAL AND ASHERAH.
ANYTIME THEY SACRIFICED ON BAAL AND
ASHERAH, THE LORD SAID ISRAEL HAS
BACKSLIDDEN because they are worshipping
other gods. They were not singing to
them. They were sacrificing TO THEM.
WHOEVER YOU SACRIFICE TO, that becomes
your God.
That's why the offering of God has been
handled casually and the Lord does not
see money. The Lord sees offering.
When when when when people gave from
Philippi,
Paul said, "I have received the things
you gave Epaphroditus."
And then he said, "But to heaven, they
are not things. It's like a
sweet-smelling aroma." But to Paul, they
were things.
You don't understand the duality of
sacrifice.
In this basket is money. In heaven, it's
an aroma.
Okay.
Son son
God is a man.
Hallelujah.
Now now
And that's why sometimes I'm sensitive
on the place of baby Jesus.
Because we have raised Sunday school
knowing that Jesus is perpetually a
baby.
And the devil has never been a child.
Have you REALIZED THAT? EVERY CHRISTMAS
PLAY, THE DEVIL IS AN [music] adult and
JESUS IS A BABY. AND THAT IS WHY EVEN
WHEN YOU ARE FACING EVEN TODAY, YOU ARE
PSYCHOLOGY OF THE DEVIL IS THAT THE
DEVIL IS TOO BIG AND UGLY, BUT JESUS IS
A BABY. THAT'S WHY WE must shout.
And then we have the suffering Messiah.
The one who ended up on the cross.
Our theology ends on the man Jesus and
the suffering Jesus. And that theology,
even the devil will sponsor it.
Because you have just portrayed your
savior as a suffering man.
THAT'S WHY THE BIGGEST holiday is Good
Friday, not Resurrection Sunday.
BECAUSE THERE IS A GLOBAL AGENDA TO MAKE
OUR GOD NOT TO LOOK as our Lord.
AND THE CHURCH STOPPED PREACHING ON THE
CROSS.
BECAUSE EVANGELISM
ENDS AT THE CROSS, BUT DISCIPLESHIP
BEGINS after the cross.
I'll repeat.
When we GO TO EVANGELIZE, WE TELL MEN
WHAT JESUS HAS DONE for us.
WHEN WE BEGIN TO DISCIPLE, WE CANNOT
stick on the cross.
WE MUST NOW INTRODUCE THE RESURRECTED
MESSIAH AND INTRODUCE THE GLORIFIED
MESSIAH.
THE AUTHORITY OF THE CHURCH IS NOT IN
THE RESURRECTED ONLY. It's in the
glorified.
Now, listen.
So, there is the man Jesus, the
suffering Jesus.
And then there is the resurrected, the
one that conquered death. The
resurrection, he conquered death, went
to Hades, took the keys, ascended. When
he was ascending, he was conquering the
realms of the spirit. He was conquering
wickedness in heavenly places. He was
conquering powers. He was conquering
principalities. He was conquering
rulers. He went above dominions and
thrones and he sat. That was the mystery
of his ascension. There is no spiritual
rank demonically that could hinder him.
I like the way you are looking at me.
I'll go slowly.
Yes?
Oh, I'm sorry. Um we are not here to
give wives. We are not here to give
cars.
I'm not here to say I I I I I I I I I I
I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I
I
Me, I'll give you the word and the word
will form a system in you and that
system will
THESE THINGS MEN ARE SEEKING AFTER, THEY
WILL FOLLOW YOU.
MY MY MIND IS TO RAISE MEN THAT ARE ARE
PURSUED BY WHAT MEN are pursuing.
Now.
SO,
WHEN HE ASCENDED, HE NOW SETTLED.
THERE are very few people that met him
in his GLORIFIED STATUS.
THE ONE THAT SAW HIM IN THAT LEVEL WAS
STEPHEN.
WHEN THEY WAS STONING HIM, HE SAID, "I
SEE JESUS."
THE FIRST MARTYR WAS GIVEN A STANDING
OVATION. HE NEVER SAW WHAT MEN SAW ON
THE CROSS. HE SAW HIM IN his glory. LET
ME EXPLAIN WHAT IT MEANS TO BE IN HIS
GLORY. BECAUSE PHILIPPIANS SAYS THAT HE
ABANDONED HIS GLORY, HUMBLED HIMSELF
UNTO DEATH AND THE DEATH of the cross.
SO, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN? HE ABANDONED
GLORY.
THERE WAS A DAY THE FORMER president
the former president
Uhuru Muigai Kenyatta used to have a
problem with his protocol team because
enough times he would sneak out of State
House.
And and you know, THAT'S A SECURITY
BREACH.
SO, ONE DAY HE SNEAKED OUT
AND HE WAS FOUND IN TRAFFIC.
WHAT THE MAN DID NOT KNOW, HE WAS STILL
THE PRESIDENT, BUT HE HAD ABANDONED
GLORY.
IS SOMEONE GETTING ME? BECAUSE THE GLORY
OF THAT MAN WAS THE MOTORCADE, THE CHASE
CARS. ONE DAY I WAS GOING TO THE AIRPORT
AND AND I TELL YOU I MET HIM IN HIS
GLORY.
AND I FELT LIKE TELLING HIM IF YOU KNEW
THE GIFT OF GOD,
BUT
THEN I SAW THE FIRST CHASE CAR, THE
SECOND ONE, THE THIRD ONE AND I REALIZED
THE PRESIDENT WAS GOING TO THE AIRPORT
BECAUSE AT THAT TIME HE WAS IN HIS
GLORY. SO, THE HAWKER MET THE PRESIDENT
not in his glory. SO, WHAT JESUS DID, HE
ABANDONED GLORY AND TOOK THE FORM OF A
MAN. BUT TODAY, HE'S NOT JUST A MAN. HE
IS THE KING JESUS IN HIS GLORY, POWER
AND MAJESTY RULING AND REIGNING OVER THE
AFFAIRS OF MEN. SO, UNTIL THE CHURCH
GETS TO KNOW THE GLORIFIED MESSIAH,
WHY? BECAUSE THE GLORIFIED MESSIAH IS
NOT ATTACHED TO THINGS. YOU JUST NEED TO
KNOW THE KING RULETH OVER THE AFFAIRS OF
MEN.
THE ONE [screaming] PAUL MET IS NOT THE
ONE PETER SAW.
PETER SAW HIM AFTER RESURRECTION. HE HAD
NOT ENTERED GLORY. BUT THE ONE PAUL MET
HAD ENTERED GLORY. THE BIBLE SAYS THE
RADIANCE OF HIS GLORY, PAUL COULD
[music] NOT EVEN LOOK AT HIM BECAUSE THE
THE THE LIGHT THAT CAME FROM HIM, THAT
WAS THE RADIATION OF THE GLORY, WAS SO
POWERFUL. IT WAS LIKE THE SUN in the DAY
STRONG.
AND PAUL heard a voice.
AND AFTER THAT ENCOUNTER,
PAUL DID NOT BEGIN a ministry as Paul.
He was told, "Go to Damascus.
You will meet a disciple, NOT AN
APOSTLE.
NOT A BISHOP, A MAN. AND THAT MAN WILL
LAY HANDS ON YOU and things will fall."
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN OUR DAY? I HAVE
HEARD OUR GENERATION SAY, "MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH GOD IS PERSONAL."
LISTEN, IT IS PERSONAL, YES, BUT GOD IS
A GOD OF MEN. HE will lead you to
ANANIAS TO TAKE AWAY THE SCALES OF YOUR
EYES. THOUGH YOU HAVE MET THE LIGHT,
IS IT MY CHANCE TO DO YOU HAVE QUALITY?
LISTEN, PRAY TO KNOW THE REAL ONE.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY, GOD IS A
PLANTER OF MEN. AND GUESS WHAT? HE WILL
NOT PLANT YOU IN AN ANGEL, IN A MAN.
IMMEDIATELY AFTER THAT, PAUL KNOWS HIS
ASSIGNMENT. HE KNOWS HE HAS BEEN CALLED
TO BE AN APOSTLE TO THE GENTILES, BUT HE
STILL has to be commissioned by an
apostolic company in Jerusalem.
The encounters of Paul are not the same
as the encounters of Peter, but at the
end of the day, he must be a son of a
man.
Sorry.
That came because of one statement.
Let's go back to scripture.
Let's go back.
The one who's there, let's go back.
Somebody say, "I must be a son of a
man."
One that we have backed, we disciple, we
raise, we anoint, we prophesy, and then
we commission.
AND THAT IS FATHERHOOD.
FATHERHOOD IS NOT WHEN I'M PARADING only
excellent sons.
Fatherhood is even when I can hold my
son who is still on diapers.
And I tell him, "You are my son, by the
way."
BECAUSE IT'S NOT THE TIME WHEN YOU
BECOME THE biggest thing in town that I
say that's my son.
No. Even in the formation stage. I
remember one day I was I I was wearing
some white garment and I was ready for
church. Then I picked my boy and I and I
was playing with him, then I I I made
him rest on my shoulder, then he vomited
on my back. And the Lord told me, "Those
are the marks of fatherhood."
Because when you are raising sons, when
they are young, they step on your toes.
When they mature, they step on your
heart.
That is the time when Pastor Jordan will
come and tell you, "You know, it's like
God has called me to another place. You
know, Pastor, I like this place.
God is not moving like before. Now I'm
entering realms, dimensions, and
mysteries. So, I feel like I need to go
to Nigeria. You know, that's where they
feel the vibe I'm feeling." And you're
like, "Boss, I taught you to pray.
I taught you the word. Now you have
outgrown your father." You know,
sometimes you always say, "Well, go."
You know, but deep down we know in the
booty. This is not another dimension in
the booty. Because no matter Do you
know, most of you are more learned than
your parents.
But you honor your parents. Why? Because
it is not about what you know, it's
about the grace they carry.
Can I give an example?
Do you know the father I'll mention the
name, the father of Papa Leo.
Papa Leo has a glass cathedral in
Mombasa, the first one to be built in
Kenya. The father of Papa Leo is Bishop
Mutua here in Mumba in Machakos.
Yes, I I I I saw where the man has been.
He's an old man who has taught prayer
and righteousness. But guess the grace
that Papa Leo needed from Bishop Mutua.
It was the grace of prayer, and that's
the father of Papa Leo Papa Leo. Because
everything Papa Leo has had to be backed
by prayer. He needed a man that carries
the grace of prayer to release the grace
upon him for exploits to happen upon his
life.
Tell your neighbor you need a man.
Oh oh oh, not your kind of man, way.
I have to complete the next sentence.
A grace CARRIER. AND YOU ALSO HAVE TO
EMPHASIZE THAT YOU NEED A MAN. YOU MAKE
ME SOUND LIKE A MAN. NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT
I'M SAYING.
SO, LET'S GO TO THE NEXT ONE. LET'S GO
TO THE next one. I have limited time.
So, THEY SAY IT SOME SAY JOHN THE
BAPTIST, SOME ELIJAH, AND OTHERS
JEREMIAH OR ONE of the prophets. Let's
look at 15. Then he asked them and he
said to them, "But who DO YOU SAY THAT I
am?"
SIMON PETER ANSWERED AND SAID, "YOU ARE
THE CHRIST, THE SON OF THE LIVING GOD."
REMEMBER WE HAVE SAID THERE ARE FOUR
DIMENSIONS OF HIM. YOU CAN KNOW HIM AS
THE MAN JESUS, THE SUFFERING JESUS, THE
RESURRECTED JESUS, or the GLORIFIED
JESUS.
THE POWER OF THE CHURCH IS AFTER
CALVARY.
WHEN WE BEGIN to teach the Jesus that is
resurrected, rose, and ascended, and is
seated, we begin to raise powerful
generals. When we begin TO TEACH THE
SUFFERING MESSIAH, we are going to help
him with our seeds and our money BECAUSE
OUR FAITH WILL need to be supported.
That's why it's called the complete work
of Calvary. We can't complete it. It's
already done. And and you ARE THE
CHRIST, THE SON OF THE LIVING GOD. LOOK
at this. Then he said, "Jesus answered
and said to him, 'BLESSED ARE YOU, SIMON
BARJONA.'" THIS MEANS SON OF JONA. "FOR
FLESH AND BLOOD HAS NOT REVEALED THIS TO
YOU, BUT MY FATHER who is in heaven."
Look at 18. "And also I SAID TO YOU THAT
YOU ARE PETER, and on this rock I will
build my church and the gates of Hades
shall NOT PREVAIL." SO, JESUS COMES TO
THIS AREA WHERE ROCKS BEAR DIFFERENT
NAMES. Just give me a few minutes and
then I'll be done. ROCKS BEAR DIFFERENT
NAMES. AND HE ASKED THEM HE'S THE ROCK
OF AGES. HE ASKED THEM, "Who do men say
that I am?" And they give him
descriptions of different prophets. They
were saying the truth, but it was not
the truth he was looking for. Because
every prophet in the Old TESTAMENT WAS A
CARRIER OF THE SPIRIT OF GOD. AND JESUS
CARRIED THE SPIRIT OF GOD WITHOUT
MEASURE. MEANING THAT IF JEREMIAH
CARRIED A DIMENSION OF THE HOLY GHOST,
THERE A MASTER BEEN A DIMENSION OF JESUS
THAT MANIFESTED LIKE JEREMIAH. IF ELIJAH
CARRIED A DIMENSION OF THE HOLY SPIRIT,
THERE A MASTER BEEN A PLACE WHERE JESUS
BEHAVED LIKE ELIJAH. SO, THIS WAS
PARTIALLY TRUE BECAUSE THE HOLY SPIRIT
WAS IN him and upon him without measure.
IN THE OLD TESTAMENT, they used to say
that THE SPIRIT CAME UPON me and I
prophesied. THAT SPIRIT THAT CAME UPON
THEM came in Jesus without measure.
AND THEN PETER NOW RISES AND SAYS, "NO,
YOU MUST BE THE CHRIST."
THE CHRIST, THE SON OF THE LIVING GOD.
And he looks at him AND HE SAID, "FLESH
AND BLOOD
>> [screaming]
>> HAS NOT REVEALED THIS TO YOU."
AND I DISCOVERED THERE ARE THREE LEVELS
OF KNOWING JESUS. THERE ARE THREE LEVELS
OR DIMENSIONS OF KNOWING JESUS.
NUMBER ONE, YOU CAN KNOW HIM BY
ENCOUNTERS.
YOU CAN KNOW HIM BY ENCOUNTERS.
THERE ARE MANY SAMPLES IN THE BIBLE THAT
ENCOUNTERED THE LORD, BUT THEY never
knew the Lord.
Moses was one OF THEM.
MOSES SEES A BUSH ON FIRE, AND THAT BUSH
IS THE LORD.
BUT AFTER THAT ENCOUNTER IS WHEN HE
DISCOVERED, "I HAVE ACTUALLY MET THE
LORD."
ENCOUNTER IS A SYSTEM OF knowing Jesus.
Are we together?
BUT THIS IS THE PROBLEM. ENCOUNTER
WITHOUT REVELATION IS LIMITED.
BECAUSE THE SECOND [music] DIMENSION OF
KNOWING JESUS IS by revelation.
BY REVELATION.
AND THERE ARE DIFFERENT DIMENSIONS OF
REVELATION.
THERE ARE CAN BE AN INNER WITNESS
AND CONFIRMATION AND AFFIRMATION, BUT
THERE CAN ALSO BE AN external
declaration. Two of them. THERE IS AN
INNER WITNESS THAT can tell you this is
him.
BUT THERE IS ALSO EXTERNAL declaration
like I'm doing right now, TEACHING.
SO, NUMBER ONE, YOU CAN KNOW GOD BY
ENCOUNTER. ALLOW ME TO SAY THIS. This is
the problem with us, especially young
people, and especially many people in
church today. Many people have had
encounters of God, but they have never
known the God of the encounter.
That's why Pastor Jordan I'm now
becoming slowly I'm I'm coming I'm I'm
coming from a point of not just laying
hands on seeing the power move. BECAUSE
PASTOR SAMUEL CUT, MANY PEOPLE are
having godly encounters, but they cannot
describe it. THEY ARE LIKE THE MAN
HEALED IN THE POOL OF BETHESDA THAT THE
MAN IS THERE FOR 38 YEARS. THE MAN HAS
AN INFIRMITY. NOTHING COULD SORT HIM
OUT. JESUS COMES AND ASKS HIM, "DO YOU
WANT TO BE HEALED?" HE SAYS THERE IS NO
MAN TO PULL me into the pool. And then
HE SAYS, "PLEASE CARRY YOUR MAT AND GO."
THEN HE MEETS THE PHARISEES AND THEY ASK
HIM, "WHO HEALED YOU?" HE SAID, "I DON'T
KNOW. I KNOW IT WAS SABBATH AND someone
said carry the mat and go." THERE ARE
PEOPLE WHO HAVE GOD DOORS. THEY HAVE
GODLY MIRACLES. INDEED, they cannot
[music] deny this can only be God, but
they don't know that God.
And that's WHY THERE ARE TIMES WHEN GOD
WILL INTRODUCE HIMSELF IN POWER.
AND PEOPLE WILL FALL UNDER THE
ANOINTING, EVEN UNBELIEVERS. PEOPLE WILL
PROPHESY, BUT AFTER THE DEMONSTRATION OF
POWER, IT IS TIME TO DISCIPLE. THAT'S
WHY NOW WE BEGIN TO TELL THEM WHO GOD
IS.
VERY FEW BELIEVERS can articulate in A
ONE-PAGER AND DESCRIBE WHOM THEY have
believed in.
VERY FEW. IF I TELL YOU, "NEXT WHEN WE
MEET, BRING A 400-WORD PAGE DESCRIBING
JESUS." VERY FEW CAN DO IT.
BECAUSE WE ARE HAVING JESUS ENCOUNTERS,
[music]
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE JESUS REVELATION.
AND THAT'S WHY IT IS REVELATION THAT
BRINGS STABILITY. [music]
ENCOUNTERS ARE GOOD, BUT revelations are
better.
Hallelujah.
REVELATION. HE ANSWERED, "FLESH."
MEANING THAT THERE CAN BE A WITNESS OF
THE SPIRIT THAT THIS IS GOD. THAT'S WHY
THE HOLY SPIRIT CAN OPEN YOUR EYES TO
REVEAL JESUS, BUT THERE CAN ALSO
REVELATION through teachings like WHAT
WE ARE DOING.
I DISCOVERED THE ENEMY IS NOT AFRAID OF
ASSEMBLIES. THE ENEMY IS AFRAID OF
TEACHINGS.
BECAUSE AND ESPECIALLY WHERE THERE IS
TEACHING OF TRUE DOCTRINE. BECAUSE YOU
CAN NEVER EXPORT MIRACLES, BUT you can
export doctrine.
Let me even explain.
Encounters are congregational, but
teachings are generational.
You can have an If I can have an
encounter of Jesus, my daughter will not
be affected.
BUT WHAT KNOW ABOUT JESUS, I can teach
my daughter.
YOU KNOW, WE ADMIRE NIGERIA. GO AND
STUDY THE HISTORY OF NIGERIA.
NIGERIA
YOU SEE FOR KENYA
KENYA, THE PENTECOSTAL MOVEMENT BEGAN IN
THE '70s with a TENDERNESS REVIVAL.
THE FIRST PENTECOSTAL MOVEMENT IN
NIGERIA WAS IN 1901. It was KAG. Kenya
I'm not Kenya, it was Assemblies of God.
THE THE FOUNDATION OF NIGERIAN LAND IS
PENTECOSTAL. THE FOUNDATION OF KENYAN
LAND IS MAINSTREAM.
THAT'S why Oh, would you kind I go a
LITTLE BIT APOSTOLIC? THAT'S WHY MOST OF
US CAME FROM THE MAINSTREAM AND WE ARE
PENTECOSTALS. AND NOW WE HAVE ENTERED
INTO WHAT WE CALL REFORMED PENTECOSTALS.
BUT TODAY, YOU CANNOT KNOW WHEN YOU LOOK
ON A POSTER TODAY, IF YOU LOOK ON AN
ORDINATION [music] POSTER OF A
PENTECOSTAL PREACHER, YOU CANNOT KNOW
WHETHER YOU'RE IN ROME, GREEK, OR KENYA.
AND I'M SPEAKING IN PARABLES. BECAUSE
THE SAME GARMENTS IN ROME HAVE NOW FOUND
EXPRESSION EVEN
AND WE USED to call THEM DINI.
BECAUSE OUR ROOTS ARE THERE. BUT THE
ROOTS OF NIGERIA, WHERE DID THEY COME
FROM? THEY BEGAN WITH PENTECOSTAL. SO,
WE ARE LOOKING AT MORE THAN 100 YEARS OF
PENTECOSTAL DOCTRINE.
AND THE CUSTODIANS THAT CARRIED THE
MESSAGE AND THE FIRE, THEY TAUGHT
NOTHING BUT THE SCRIPTURE.
THEY TAUGHT PEOPLE THE WORD OF GOD. THEY
TAUGHT THEM DOCTRINE, NOT PHILOSOPHIES
OF MEN. SO, BY THE TIME WE ARE GATHERING
IN STADIUMS TO LISTEN TO THAT
GENERATION, THEY ARE FATHERS THAT
LABORED THAT YOU ENTER A CHURCH,
MYSTERIES ARE ORDINARY STATEMENTS.
>> [music]
>> Whatever we call MYSTERIES HERE
I ATTENDED A CHURCH IN NIGERIA. I WAS
THE ONLY ONE WRITING NOTES.
BECAUSE I'M HEARING THEM FOR THE FIRST
TIME. BUT FOR THEM, THIS IS COMMON.
FOR THEM, THEY ALWAYS ARGUE WITH TIME.
THEY WILL SAY, "YOU KNOW, I don't have
time. I would have expounded on that
mystery." HERE, WE HAVE NOT EVEN ENTERED
MYSTERIES. WE ARE still in the Oh, WE
ARE STILL IN THE REALM OF EVANGELISM.
BECAUSE THE AND I'M NOT HERE TO
CRITICIZE BECAUSE WE MUST MIGRATE. THE
THE PEOPLE preaching to us were
evangelists. So, WHEN THEY DISCOVERED
THE WAVE OF THE WAVE OF CRUSADES ARE
OVER, THEY JUST changed their name
evangelist to pastor. BUT WHEN YOU GO ON
SUNDAY, YOU DON'T HEAR TEACHINGS. YOU
ARE STILL IN A CRUSADE GROUND.
ONE SCRIPTURE.
YOU SEE OH MY GOD.
YOU CAN'T GROW A CHURCH BY THAT VOICE.
BUT YOU CAN [music] GATHER MEN BY THAT
VOICE.
AND I'M HERE TO appreciate evangelists.
But you cannot evangelize a
congregation.
And we confused shouting
for power.
Go and look at the most the man I
respect a a lot, E.A. Adeboye.
>> [music]
>> He has the biggest church, a million
seater. He still preaches with a mic
that has a cord. He doesn't shout.
Yeah uh
Edwin was in his church. He said he
finished a meeting and he said, "Lord,
visit your people." 200 [music] cripples
walked.
That is how he finished the service.
"Lord, meet your people." He left.
Wheelchairs
were left at Kenyatta Avenue. You see
And THEN IF NOTHING HAPPENS
WE WILL TELL YOU MUNGU ANAKUPENDA pole
pole. Itafunguka.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR WE NEED REVELATION.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR BEYOND ENCOUNTERS
WE NEED REVELATION.
THAT'S WHY HE SAYS FLESH AND BLOOD DOES
NOT WHAT? DOES NOT REVEAL. WE NEED THE
HOLY [screaming] GHOST TO BEGIN TO OPEN
OUR EYES TO KNOW HIM AS HE IS.
THE THAT LEVEL of knowing Jesus is by
eternal truths.
Eternal truths.
THEY ARE TRUTHS ABOUT HIM THAT DON'T
CHANGE.
NO MATTER WHICH generation comes and go.
They are truths about him.
Omniscient, omnipotent, omnipresent,
sovereign, majesty, Lord.
These are dimensions of knowing him.
THEN HE SAYS, "YOU KNOW, JOHN, THIS DOES
NOT THIS IS NOT FLESH AND BLOOD."
MEANING THAT WHEN THE CHURCH ENTERS THE
revelation of Jesus
And we we of course WE BUILD IT UP from
the man Jesus. We come to the death and
then we come to the resurrected, the
glorified. We have to build that order.
BUT WHEN THE CHURCH COMES TO THE
revelation when the church comes he
said, "YOU KNOW, UPON THIS ROCK
WHAT IS THAT ROCK? I will build my
church
upon this rock. I WILL BUILD MY CHURCH."
VERY POWERFUL.
THAT THAT WORD THERE IN GREEK IS PETROS
AND PETRAS.
HE SAID, "FROM TODAY, OH PETER, YOU
SHALL BECOME A ROCK, A PETROS, A SMALL
ROCK. A LANGUAGE OF STABILITY AND
STATURE.
BUT HE SAID, "UPON THIS PETRAS
YOU CAN'T BUILD A CHURCH ON A MAN.
THE CHURCH CAN ONLY BE BUILT [music] ON
JESUS. HE SAID, "UPON THIS PETRAS, BIG
ROCK
BECAUSE WE'RE IN A ECONOMY OF ROCKS. I
WILL BUILD my church." Now, listen and
I'm about to bring a few politics. The
word church there is ecclesia.
Ecclesia.
That word ecclesia was borrowed from the
Greek rendering.
And it is not what we call church today.
And that's why
the mandate of God cannot be carried by
the church. It can only be carried by
the ecclesia.
Until the church becomes ecclesia the
prophecies and the mandate of God will
be carried out.
Because the stability was not on
institution, it was on a system called
ecclesia.
Hi.
Pastor, what do you mean? I I run a
church called Life Church.
Until I change that church from the
system of denomination to ecclesia, the
mandate and the government of God cannot
be carried by the system we have
established.
That's why WHEN WE LOOK AT WHAT WE CALL
THE CHURCH TODAY, is one
I'm saying this with a lot of love. When
we look at the church and we begin to
look at the results, there is a lot of
defeat yet a lot of child shout.
When we look at it in Kenya, do you KNOW
IF THE CHURCH was raptured today if
those who call themselves believers were
to be raptured today, the economy of
Kenya will not shake.
Because we only we we we only contribute
3% of the economy. The economy of this
land is owned by Indians, 50%. 30% by
Muslim, 17% by multinationals, 3% to
cooperate. CC Walevi wavuta bangi
wakristo. We are fighting for that
percentage. But look at how we shout. DO
YOU KNOW WHEN I WAS COMING HERE GOD
ASHAMED? I SAW WHAT homeboys were
setting up there. Then I saw what we
have set up and we are the church. I
said, "Lord,
I don't know if you've seen THE SOUND
THERE.
SECULAR MEN WHO DON'T KNOW GOD.
And here we must put speakers on Angkor
Theta.
SO THAT THAT SIDE CAN HEAR. THIS SIDE
CAN HEAR.
MEN HAVE SPEAKERS IN THE CAR. AND YET WE
ARE HERE SAYING, "HE THAT IS IN ME IS
GREATER THAN HE THAT IS IN THE WORLD.
WHERE MY FOOT STEP AT, THAT SHALL BE MY
GOD." WE NEED TO TURN DOWN ON THE
GLAMOUR AND MAKE THE CHURCH TO BE the
ecclesia first.
>> [applause]
>> NOW, WHAT WAS THE PROBLEM? THE NAME
ECCLESIA IS A GOVERNMENT
THAT CARRIES POWER, [screaming]
LEGISLATIVE POWER,
JUDICIAL POWER, AND GOVERNMENTAL POWER.
AN ECCLESIA WAS AN ASSEMBLY of selected
men that dictated the affair of a
territory. I will repeat.
An ecclesia, according to the Greek,
NIKAMA LEO USEME
"UPON THIS ROCK, I will build my
parliament."
WE ALL KNOW WHAT parliament is.
Men that are voted representing
different regions, they can gather there
and impeach a man.
We know what it is, okay?
But when we WANT THEM TO DISCUSS ABOUT
SERIOUS MATTERS LIKE ADANI, there's no
quorum. But when it is impeaching A MAN,
THEY ARE THERE, FULL HOUSE.
SO, THAT TELLS ME THE AFFAIRS OF THE
TERRITORY IS AT THE MERCIES of a
building where men gather.
SO, WHEN GOD WAS LOOKING AT THE EARTH,
HE REALIZED, "I MUST SELECT SOME MEN.
GATHER THOSE MEN NOT IN A BUILDING ONLY,
BUT IN AN ASSEMBLY. AND IN THAT
ASSEMBLY, THEY HAVE JUDICIAL POWER.
THEY HAVE LEGISLATIVE POWER AND THEY
HAVE GOVERNMENTAL POWER. THAT'S THE
CHURCH.
THAT'S THE CHURCH.
PEOPLE LIKE KARL MARX CAME AND CALLED
THE CHURCH THE OPIUM of the poor and it
LOOKS LIKE SO.
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE CHURCHES THAT
THRIVE BY GIVING BREAD. DO YOU KNOW THE
PATTERN OF THE APOSTLES WAS NONE AMONG
THEM LACKED.
THE CHURCH WAS NOT A BREAD AND UNGA
DISTRIBUTION CENTER. THE CHURCH WAS WHEN
YOU GATHERED AMONG THEM, THEY BROUGHT
THEIR STUFF TOGETHER.
AND THE BIBLE SAYS, "THEM THAT WERE THEM
WITH THEM, NONE LACKED." MEANING THAT
outside some were hungry.
And what brought them was apostolic
doctrine, prayer. It was NOT HUNGER.
WE ARE NOT
NGOS.
WE ARE NOT SOCIAL ENTITIES. WE ARE
SPIRITUAL EPICENTERS.
IT'S A GOVERNMENT.
AND THAT'S WHY
WHEN THE GREEK HAD, especially the
territories that were governed by the
Greek people, when they heard OF THE
WORD ECCLESIA, BECAUSE OF POLITICAL
FEARS, THEY NEVER permitted that word to
be interpreted as ecclesia. They wanted
it to be interpreted as church. What is
the name church?
The name church
when you go to the root word,
Eugene, it comes from the word circus.
And a circus
was
people who were surrounding an altar
offering sacrifice to the sun god. It is
an ancient Rome culture. That's why the
early church architectural designs were
sacral in nature, and the rooftop had to
allow the sun to enter because the altar
was for the sun god. That's where the
name circus came from, where people
surround an altar and make sacrifice to
the sun god.
That's where the name church came. And
even today, we come to surround an
altar, and one powerful man who has 3 kg
Bible, 2 kg bling bling cross, because
no one knows the very Holy Spirit in you
is the very Holy Spirit in him.
So, it's we are still Oh.
We are still back in the circus.
And then you enrich us.
And then we make sure revelation is
rare. Because if you know what I know, I
your clientship is over.
Because I need YOU EVERY SUNDAY.
GOD NEVER LEFT SERVICES. GOD left
fellowship.
FELLOWSHIP IS WHATEVER I KNOW, YOU KNOW.
THE SPIRIT IN ME is in you.
DO YOU KNOW IN THE EARLY GATHERINGS IN
THE SYNAGOGUE, there was no pastor?
DO YOU KNOW THE NAME PASTOR APPEARS TWO
TIMES IN THE NEW TESTAMENT? YET WE HAVE
MORE PASTORS MORE THAN APOSTLES,
PROPHETS, TEACHERS, and evangelists.
IT APPEARS TWO TIMES, PASTOR, THE NAME
PASTOR. ALL THEOLOGY SCHOOLS ARE
PRODUCING PASTORS, NOT APOSTLES.
BECAUSE THE GOVERNMENTAL ORDER OF
ECCLESIA NEEDS APOSTOLIC GRACES. THESE
ARE MEN that are territorial. It needs
prophets. WHATEVER WE ARE SEEING TODAY,
THOSE ARE NOT PROPHETS, THOSE ARE SEERS.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A PROPHET
AND A SEER. A SEER A SEER CAN SEE SOCIAL
MATTERS.
OH, SAUL
IS LOOKING FOR LOST DONKEYS. SAUL DOES
NOT NEED A PROPHET, HE NEEDS A SEER.
BECAUSE GOD CANNOT INVEST INTELLIGENCE
AND ANOINTING IN A PROPHET TO LOOK FOR
DONKEYS.
THE BIBLE SAYS, "BY THE WORD OF A
PROPHET, ISRAEL ISRAEL WERE DELIVERED."
WORD.
WORD. THESE ARE TERRITORIAL,
GOVERNMENTAL, THAT A MAN CAN DECLARE,
"TOMORROW SUCH A TIME, THERE SHALL BE
SUPPLY." WORD.
NOT THOSE ONES WHO ARE SINGING. DO I
KNOW YOU, MAN OF GOD? I DON'T know you.
You sing. I see I see sound. I say, "Go
deeper." I see music. Go deeper. I see
hit songs.
I see something like this.
And then you say, "GO DEEP." NO, NO,
THOSE ARE SEERS. THEY CAN THEY SEE
social matters. And I'm not here to
discredit them, they are there in the
Bible.
But when the Lord begins to bless a
nation with prophets, some of the things
you are facing will be out.
A man can stand on a on a platform and
say, "Tomorrow such a time, the chaos in
government is over."
And that word becomes law in a
territory. SO, UNTIL WE COME TO the
ecclesia [clears throat] Is someone
GETTING ME? SOMEBODY SAY ECCLESIA.
SOMEBODY SAY ECCLESIA.
THE BIBLE SAYS, "AND THE GOVERNMENT
SHALL BE UPON HIS SHOULDER."
You see, Jesus said that the prophecy
there says, "Unto us a child is born,
but unto us a son is given, AND THE
GOVERNMENT SHALL be upon his shoulder."
What does that mean? Where does the body
begin? FROM THE SHOULDER.
SO, JESUS IS THE HEAD, BUT THE
GOVERNMENT OF HEAVEN IS UPON the body.
What is the body? IT'S THE ECCLESIA. SO,
THE GOVERNMENT OF HEAVEN CANNOT BE
EXPRESSED ON EARTH UNTIL the formation
of the church TUNES TO THE PATTERNS of
ecclesia.
Are you getting what I'M SAYING?
MEANING THAT WHATEVER IS HAPPENING IN
KENYA, YOU KNOW THEY ALWAYS SAY THE WORK
OF THE CHURCH IS TO PRAY, BUT THEY DON'T
KNOW WHY. BECAUSE THE ECCLESIA IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE TERRITORY.
BUT WHAT has happened, and I have no
time now, what has happened, the
ecclesia has been corrupted by Babylon.
That's why we have the church in
Revelation is being called out of
Jezebel, is being called OUT OF BABYLON,
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T CHANGE BABYLON WHEN
you are in BABYLON SYSTEM.
THE CALLING OUT OF THE CHURCH IS OUT OF
THAT GOVERNMENT THAT CONTROLS THE WORLD,
BECAUSE THE CHURCH CANNOT BE THE
CONTROLLING POWER WHEN IT IS UNDER THE
BABYLONIAN PATTERNS.
THERE MUST BE THE APOSTOLIC AND THE
PROPHETIC BLUEPRINT for the ecclesia,
the government OF GOD.
THE MAN THAT BECAME RESPONSIBLE to make
sure the names were changed,
one of them was King James. When he was
When he was rewriting the the the
grammar, he said, "You guys you cannot
put the name church."
And in more than 102 or 122 times, only
two times is the church referred as
ecclesia. 120 times it was called church
to create a mindset of congregation, and
not a mindset of government.
Hey.
"Upon this rock, I will build my
ecclesia." When the ecclesia is
gathered, revival is a small matter.
That's a force of revolution.
That's why I'm believing God. I'm not
believing God of a revival to heal the
sick. I'm believing God of a revolution
that a man like Joseph can arise out of
such a meeting and give government's
proposal that Africa will be out of
poverty in less than a generation. IT IS
MORE POWERFUL THAN ONE WALKING.
THAT A DIVINE IDEA CAN LAND ON YOU, AND
YOU COME UP WITH AN INNOVATION THAT WILL
HELP generations after you. IT IS MORE
POWERFUL THAN ONE BLIND EYE BEING
OPENED. WE WERE LIMITED IN OUR SIGHT
WHEN IT CAME TO POWER, BUT I WANT TO
BELIEVE THIS TIME THE LORD IS NOT
raising small men.
HE'S
I I LOOKED AT SOMEONE AND I SAID,
"TODAY, A MAN LIKE ELON MUSK, HE'S THE
FACE OF INNOVATION WITHOUT HOLY GHOST."
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE BOOK OF ROMANS I'M
NOT ROMANS, HEBREW. THE BIBLE SAYS,
"THESE MEN BROUGHT THE DEAD BACK TO
LIFE. THEY DID WONDROUS THINGS IN THEIR
DAY, THOUGH THE PROMISE WAS NOT UPON
THEM." NOW, WE HAVE THE HOLY GHOST.
GUESS WHAT WE HAVE DONE TO THE HOLY
GHOST? WE HAVE CONFINED HIM INTO A
LANGUAGE.
THAT ALL YOU CAN DO AS A PENTECOSTAL IS
ABRACADABRA LABADASHADA. AND NOW, ALL WE
DO IS PRAY IN THE LANGUAGE WHAT WE DON'T
UNDERSTAND. HE IS THE GIFT OF [music]
PROMISE. WHEN WE GET TO UNDERSTAND THE
FUNCTION OF THE HOLY GHOST, IT'S BEYOND
THE LANGUAGE, IT'S AN IMPARTATION. YOU
SHALL RECEIVE POWER WHEN THE HOLY GHOST
COMES UPON YOU, AND YOU SHALL BE MY
WITNESSES.
A CARRIER OF EVIDENCE GLOBALLY THAT
JESUS IS NO LONGER in the grave, he's
glorified. He's in THE HEAVENLY PLACES.
THOSE ARE THE MEN THAT THE LORD IS
looking for. WE ARE GOING [music] BEYOND
CHURCH. TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR,
WE ARE GOING BEYOND CHURCH."
THAT'S WHY A GOVERNMENT CANNOT BE FORMED
BY CITY LIGHT ONLY. A GOVERNMENT CANNOT
BE FORMED BY LIFE CHURCH ONLY. A
GOVERNMENT CANNOT BE FORMED BY RAIN CITY
ONLY. A GOVERNMENT IS A CONVERGENCE OF
GRACES. IT'S WHEN MEN COME TOGETHER AND
BEGIN TO SHAKE THE SYSTEMS THAT ARE
THERE. AND I'M BELIEVING GOD. I AM NOT
SAYING FOR YOU TO BE CHURCHLESS, YOU
MUST BE UNDER A MAN, SON OF MAN, BUT
UPON THIS ROCK UPON [music] THIS ROCK
revelation of Jesus, IT WILL BEGIN TO
GATHER US AS A GOVERNMENT. BECAUSE IF
[music] THE GOVERNMENT OF GOD IS NOT
EXISTING ON THE EARTH, Babylon will RULE
US.
>> [music]
>> THE PROBLEMS WE HAVE IN OUR LAND TODAY
IS NOT A PRAYER ISSUE. ROADS DON'T NEED
PRAYER. WATER DOES NOT NEED PRAYER.
HEALTH DOES NOT NEED PRAYER. WE JUST
NEED MEN THAT CARRY ANOTHER SYSTEM,
WHICH IS NOT A SYSTEM OF CORRUPTION. IT
JUST NEED MEN THAT ARE CULTURED [music]
LIKE DANIEL. THEY CARRY THE
CONSCIOUSNESS OF HUMANITY. HOW? WHO
SHALL USHER THAT GOVERNMENT? [music] IT
MUST COME FROM ANOTHER REALM, because
this one in this realm cannot work.
THAT'S WHY THE CHURCH MUST ARISE.
THIS I REFUSE TO PRAY WITHOUT [music]
INTELLIGENCE. I SHALL HOLD THE
NEWSPAPER, hold news, and hold MY BIBLE,
AND ASK THE LORD, "What is the matter
concerning Kenya?" Because there must be
a spiritual government that is taking
over.
Our relevance is not there.
Me, I'm tired of being called in
meetings where all we do is open with a
word of prayer.
And then you see and see people scatter
in Kenya. [music]
A time has come after opening with a
word of prayer, I can wear my PhD and
become a consultant in matters
economics.
Because until until we raise men of such
caliber, we have failed.
We have failed.
I'm I'm coming to a place where I
believe that God is calling the church
back to ecclesia. Tell your neighbor,
"Neighbor, legislative,
judicial, governmental powers."
This was the fear of Rome. It was the
fear of the Greek. They never wanted the
Ecclesia to manifest. Up to date is the
fear of the devil. But by this
revelation, the church is rising. Please
stand up on your feet. Stand up on your
feet.
>> [music]
>> I remember when TD Jakes came in Kenya.
Let me receive the worshipers. This is
what he said. This is what TD Jakes
said. He said, "Things like boreholes
are not things you pray for. These are
things that are brought by good
governance."
There are things we are praying for. We
are wasting prayer.
We just need to culture system in man.
I am believing God that the Josiah
revival will happen.
The revival of the word.
I'm sorry. I have hurried because time
is not enough and I had to finish there.
But when God creates time next time,
I'm moving from preaching to
conversation. We shall build it from
there.
We need to know Jesus.
Because you also need to understand what
are the gates of heads.
>> [music]
>> How are these gates opened?
When the gates of hell are opened, HOW
DO THEY BEGIN TO AFFECT A TERRITORY?
ONE OF THE WAYS PEOPLE open gates of
hell is by war.
The war in Congo cannot end by civil
negotiation. They are gates that have to
be closed.
Because when human blood is shed in
intensity,
gates are opened spiritually.
THAT'S WHY ANYTIME we approach an
election of seven, BECAUSE OF THE
PATTERN OF THE BLOOD IN SEVEN, WE ALWAYS
ENTER a system and a time of contention
of war because they are demonic doors
that were opened in that time.
>> [music]
>> I'm praying for 2027 now. I don't need
to wait for that time. And you can see
how THE HOW THE STIRRING spiritual and
political is already happening. If you
cannot open your eyes in the spirit and
begin to see, allow me to TELL YOU THIS.
WHATEVER IS HAPPENING IN the Senate, the
impeachment, I speak this on record. It
will begin to reflect IN ALL COUNTIES.
YOU'LL HEAR GOVERNORS BEING IMPEACHED
LEFT, RIGHT, and center BECAUSE AT THIS
HOUR THERE IS A SPIRIT of betrayal being
dispersed.
>> [music]
>> I AM NOT SUPPORTING THIS ONE OR THIS
ONE, BUT I KNOW WHEN A HOUSE DOES NOT
KNOW ITS FUNCTION. I KNOW THERE COULD BE
MANY POLITICAL WRONGS, BUT THE DEVIL
ALWAYS LOOK FOR AN EMPTY. THE DEVIL JUST
NEEDS A WOUNDED BITTER MAN AND HE WILL
USE THAT DOOR OF BITTERNESS TO USHER you
into addictions.
SO, IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT WHEN YOU ARE
WOUNDED, SOMETHING WRONG was not done.
Is someone getting me? BUT YOU SEE THAT
PAIN BECOMES A LEGAL DOOR OF ATTACK. SO,
WHATEVER IS HAPPENING POLITICALLY, THERE
ARE MANY THINGS, BUT THE ENEMY HAS FOUND
A DOOR OF ENTRY. SO THAT NOW THERE CAN
BE A STIRRING OF BETRAYAL ALL OVER. YOU
WILL SEE IT BECAUSE BECAUSE I SPEAK
UNDER THE YOU WILL SEE IT. IT WILL BE A
BROTHER BETRAYING A BROTHER. AND THAT'S
WHERE THE CHURCH WILL GET an entry
BECAUSE WHEN MEN DISCOVER THE GOVERNMENT
CANNOT HELP THEM, THEY MUST BEGIN TO cry
to another government. They must begin
TO SEEK HELP FROM ANOTHER GOVERNMENT.
THAT'S WHY THE CHURCH CANNOT BE
POLITICIZED. THE CHURCH CANNOT BE
POLITICAL. THE CHURCH MUST BECOME THE
GOVERNMENT [music]
OF GOD THAT RELEASES JUDICIAL DECREE,
THAT RELEASES LEGISLATIVE DECREE. THE
CHURCH MUST BECOME THE VOICE OF
CONSCIOUSNESS THAT SPEAKS WHERE EVIL HAS
PREVAILED. THE CHURCH CANNOT BE A PART
OF GOVERNMENT. IT HAS NEVER HAPPENED.
AND [music] I'M SAYING THIS, THE CHURCH
PRAYS FOR GOVERNMENT, BUT THE CHURCH
cannot be a part of government. BECAUSE
YOU SEE, OUR LEGISLATION IS DIFFERENT.
NOW, [music] THE THE LEGISLATION OF THE
WORLD IS WE REWARD the corrupt. THE
LEGISLATION OF THIS GOVERNMENT IS THAT
JUDGMENT SHALL BEFALL any man that robs
the innocent. NOW, YOU SEE, WE CAN'T SIT
TOGETHER AND BEGIN TO REASON BECAUSE THE
JUDICIAL [music] LEGISLATION OF MY ALTAR
IS PARALLEL TO THE POLITICAL
LEGISLATION. THAT'S WHY WHEN THE CHURCH
ARISES IN ITS RANK AS ANOTHER
GOVERNMENT, THEY NEVER agree with
governments.
>> [music]
>> Because the system is parallel.
May the church arise.
THE HOPE OF KENYA IS NOT IN A SYSTEM.
THE HOPE of Kenya is IN THE CHURCH.
PASTOR, WHY IS THE CHURCH QUIET? WE ARE
THE CHURCH.
I AM PART OF THAT ECCLESIA. YOU ARE PART
OF IT. I want us to hold hands.
I want us to hold hands because the
government of Kenya will come. I mean,
the government of God will come to the
land through Ecclesia.
Can I tell you the truth?
God cannot entrust me with the revival
of Kenya. It's a risk.
God will not entrust one man with this
revival.
We either unite and win or divide and
die like fools.
That's the only thing.
The Lord SAW WHAT HAPPENED IN THE DAYS
OF THE West revival where there was A.
A. Allen. When the man died, the move
died. Uh it cuts in Kulman. The woman
died, the move died. Ja- JACO, THE MAN
DIED, THE MOVE DIED. RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT
ABOUT A MAN. IT'S ABOUT him pouring his
spirit upon all flesh BECAUSE I BELIEVE
EVEN in this meeting, SOME OF YOU MAY
NOT KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE BEGUN. IT MAY
QUALIFY TO BE AN ECCLESIA. This is the
time for nobodies. And I'm going to
repeat.
>> [music]
>> IT IS THE SEASON FOR NOBODIES. DON'T
WAIT TO HAVE A TITLE. WHATEVER THE LORD
IS COMPELLING YOU to do, DO IT. BEGIN
THAT PRAYER IN THE OFFICE. BEGIN THAT
BIBLE STUDY IN THE OFFICE. CAN I BE
RADICAL A LITTLE BIT? CAN I BE RADICAL A
LITTLE BIT? YOU DON'T HAVE ANOTHER LIFE
TO LIVE. IF WHERE YOU ARE, THEY ARE NOT
SERIOUS WITH YOUR DESTINY AND YOUR
SPIRITUAL MATURITY, YOU BETTER RUN FOR
YOUR LIFE. THIS IS NOT THE TIME TO TO
OH, I DON'T KNOW. HOW DO How do I put it
this without LOOKING LIKE BECAUSE THERE
ARE MANY STRANGE AREAS WHERE OUR MEN ARE
BOUND AND THEY ARE NOT GROWING. YOU MUST
BE SERIOUS ABOUT YOUR SPIRITUAL GROWTH.
ANY ALTAR THAT IS NOT SENSITIVE ABOUT
YOUR RISING, RUN FOR YOUR LIFE BECAUSE
YOU DON'T [music] HAVE ANOTHER LIFE TO
LIVE. YOU CANNOT WASTE YOUR SPIRITUAL
TIME IN A PLACE WHERE THEY DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOU. IT IS TIME TO MIGRATE WITH A
LOT OF WISDOM AND A LOT of prayer. I'M
SAYING THIS BECAUSE I KNOW THERE ARE
STRANGE VOICES IN TOWN.
>> [music]
>> HALLELUJAH.
How can you bring the worship [music]
for me?
>> [music]
>> I'M BURNING SOME ALTARS. THERE ARE
THINGS THAT DON'T NEED DISCERNMENT OF
THE HOLY GHOST. THEY JUST NEED COMMON
SENSE TO KNOW THERE IS NOTHING ABOUT GOD
HERE. IT'S TIME FOR ME TO LEAVE.
WE CAN'T BRING SECULAR ARTISTS ON A
GODLY ALTAR. DON'T WE HAVE WORSHIPERS
THAT CAN BURN INCENSE ON THE ALTAR OF
YAHWEH? AND WHEN WE BEGIN TO PATTERN
[music] THAT KIND OF CULTURE, A
GENERATION WILL THINK THIS IS NOW HOW WE
WORSHIP GOD. LISTEN, THE ALTAR OF YAHWEH
IS A HOLY ALTAR. THE GLORY OF GOD CANNOT
MANIFEST IN DEFILEMENT. ANYTIME ISRAEL
FELL, IT WAS THE GLORY THAT DEPARTED.
[music]
WE need to lay the pattern BECAUSE WHEN
I DIE, I WANT TO look from glory AND
KNOW MY SON IS RECEIVING THE RIGHT
DOCTRINE. I DON'T WANT TO LOOK BACK AND
FEEL LIKE IN THE SIKU TULIKUWA MAPASI.
WE MUST BRING THE CHURCH BACK [music] TO
THE GOVERNMENTAL ORDER WHERE THE HOLY
SPIRIT IS THE ONE THAT GOVERNS THE
CHURCH. WHEN ANANIAS AND SAPPHIRA ABUSES
THE OFFERING, WE DON'T EVEN NEED TO
PRAY. THE OWNER OF THE GOVERNMENT WILL
TAKE CARE OF MEN. LET US BEGIN TO PRAY
FOR OUR LIVES. WE NEED THE GOVERNMENT OF
GOD IN OUR MINISTRIES. WE NEED IT IN OUR
LIVES. BEGIN TO TELL THE LORD, "LORD, IN
MY DAY, WHATEVER YOU HAVE [music]
PURPOSE IN THIS TIME, WE STILL HAVE
THREE MORE YEARS TO GO. WE HAVE HEARD OF
REVIVALS. WE HAVE HEARD THERE WILL BE A
MOVE OF GOD IN THIS GOVERNMENT. OH LORD,
WHATEVER YOU HAVE ANNOUNCED IN OUR TIME,
LET IT BEGIN [music] TO MANIFEST. THERE
IS A GENERATION THAT MUST ARISE IN THIS
ALTAR. RESTORE THE ECCLESIA. RESTORE THE
POWER. RESTORE THE POWER. RESTORE THE
POWER. RESTORE THE LEGISLATION. RESTORE
THE RULERSHIP. RESTORE IT IN OUR DAY.
LET THE GLORY OF THE CHURCH LET IT BE
RESTORED IN THE NAME OF JESUS. WE ARE
THE CHURCH OF THE END TIME. WE ARE THE
CHURCH OF JESUS. WE ARE THE CARRIER OF
THE MANDATE OF THIS HOUR. YOU ARE PART
OF THAT ARMY. YOU ARE PART OF THAT
LEGISLATIVE. YOU ARE PART OF THAT BODY.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music]
>> LET THE GOVERNMENT RISE. LET THE
GOVERNMENT RISE. LET THE [music]
GOVERNMENT RISE. LET THE GOVERNMENT
RISE. LET THE GOVERNMENT RISE.
>> [music]
>> JUST HOLD ON.
>> I WANT US,
with this revelation,
to pray for our nation
>> [music]
>> as another government.
Hallelujah.
As the purposes of God concerning Kenya,
what God declared will happen, it will
happen. WE ARE GOING TO MAKE THESE
PRAYERS AND I WANT TO BELIEVE GOD BY THE
TIME WE WILL GATHER AGAIN, you will see
it in the news because we have gathered
as THE CHURCH.
>> [music]
>> WE ARE NOT TEACHING THEORY.
WE ARE TEACHING THE POWER OF GOD. I WANT
US TO MAKE THREE PRAYERS. NUMBER ONE,
ANYTHING IN THIS GOVERNMENT THAT IS NOT
OF GOD, LET IT BE VOMITED. [music]
ANYTHING THAT IS NOT OF GOD, LET IT BE
VOMITED. LET IT BE VOMITED. LET IT NOT
SEE THE LIGHT OF DAY. WHATEVER
LISTEN.
ANY TIME
>> [music]
>> JUST HOLD ON.
LISTEN. WHATEVER IS HAPPENING IN KENYA
IS NOT AFFECTING YOUR MOTHER.
IT'S AFFECTING YOU AND ME DIRECTLY.
SO, WHATEVER HAPPENS THAT IS GOOD, IT IS
going to HAPPEN AFFECT YOUR BUSINESS,
YOUR CAREER, EVERYTHING YOU ARE DOING is
going TO RECEIVE A DIRECT IMPACT. SO, IF
THERE IS A WRONG SEED IN POWER, THERE
ARE PEOPLE WHO SIT LIKE RIGHT NOW WE
NEED TO PRAY FOR THE GIFTS OF KENYA. The
gifts WILL NOT BE HIJACKED. ANYONE THAT
TRIES TO HIJACK [music] THE GIFTS WILL
NOT PREVAIL. THAT THE THE LORD, THE ONE
THAT SITS IN HEAVEN, THE ONE THAT
CONTROLS THE THRONES OF MEN WILL BEGIN
TO OVERTHROW WHATEVER IS TRYING TO
OVERTHROW OUR LAND. WHATEVER THAT IS NOT
OF GOD, LIFT UP YOUR HAND AND SAY IN THE
NAME OF JESUS. WHATEVER THAT IS NOT OF
GOD
IN PARLIAMENT IN SENATE IN [music]
GOVERNMENT, WHATEVER THAT IS NOT OF GOD
IN THE NAME OF JESUS, LET IT BE ABORTED
NOW. LET IT BE ABORTED NOW. LET IT
[music] BE ABORTED NOW. LET IT BE
ABORTED NOW. WE PRAY FOR KENYA. WE PRAY
FOR THE GOVERNMENT. WE PRAY FOR THE
PRESIDENT. [music] WE PRAY FOR THE VICE.
WE PRAY FOR PARLIAMENT. WE PRAY FOR
SENATORS. WHATEVER THE BIBLE SAYS, WHEN
MEN WERE ASLEEP, THE ENEMY WAS PLANTING.
WHATEVER THAT HAS BEEN PLANTED IN OUR
SLUMBER, LET IT BE UPROOTED NOW. LET IT
BE UPROOTED NOW. LET IT BE UPROOTED NOW.
LET IT BE UPROOTED NOW. IN THE NAME OF
JESUS.
>> [music]
>> PRAYER NUMBER TWO.
OUR ECONOMY WILL CHANGE.
YES, WE REFUSE TO BE IN A PLACE OF
SABOTAGE EVERY TIME. THAT ANY TIME WE
WANT TO RISE, THERE IS A SABOTAGE. THAT
SPIRIT WILL NOT PREVAIL IN OUR LAND
BECAUSE WHEN THE ECONOMY IS AFFECTED, IT
IS THE YOUNG PEOPLE THAT ARE AFFECTED.
[laughter] LET OUR ECONOMY CHANGE. LET
THEM THAT HAVE OUR AGENDA AT HEART, LET
THEM BEGIN TO ARISE.
THE SECOND PRAYER I WANT YOU TO PRAY.
BEGIN TO TELL THE LORD, LET THE SYSTEM
OF THE KINGDOM BEGIN TO FORM IN ME. LET
THE SYSTEM OF THE KINGDOM BEGIN TO FORM
IN ME. THIS REVIVAL IS ABOUT THE KINGDOM
SYSTEM FORMING IN A MAN. LET THE KINGDOM
SYSTEM, LET [music] THE KINGDOM SYSTEM,
THE SYSTEM OF HOLINESS, THE SYSTEM OF
RIGHTEOUSNESS, THE SYSTEM OF PRAYER, THE
SYSTEM OF FAITH, THE SYSTEM OF READING
THE WORD, LET THESE CULTURES, [music]
LET THEM BECOME MY CULTURE. LIKE DANIEL
IN BABYLON, LET THE SYSTEM FORM IN ME.
LET THE SYSTEM FORM IN ME. LET THE
SYSTEM FORM IN ME. COMPROMISE WILL NOT
BE OUR ORDER. THAT A GENERAL GENERATION,
OUR PEOPLE ARE ARISING FULL OF THE HOLY
GHOST. NOTHING CAN BEND THEM. NOTHING
CAN COMPROMISE THEM. NOTHING CAN MAKE
THEM BOW. THEY HAVE VIRGIN KNEES. THEY
CANNOT BOW TO THE POWER AND THE ALTARS
OF ASHERAH. LET THE RIGHTEOUS [music]
BREED. LET IT BEGIN TO ARISE. LET THE
HOLY NATION, LET IT BEGIN TO ARISE NOW.
MAY YOU BE THE PEOPLE. LET THE SYSTEM
KATALA BADA. LET THE SYSTEM, LET THE
SYSTEM, LET THE SYSTEM OF [music] THE
KINGDOM BEGIN TO FORM.
>> [music]
>> THE FINAL PRAYER.
YEAH.
LET ME JUST HAVE Pastor
come come George.
Let's come some of us come.
Come Ronnie, you're doing something in
the city. Anyone that is doing something
in the city, just come.
>> [music]
>> We want to agree.
The city is opening up again.
>> [music]
>> The city is opening up again.
Hallelujah.
I am believing God I'll begin to hear
oh, there's a Bible study happening in
Serena.
There's a Bible study happening in
Stanley.
>> [music]
>> These are generals.
These are CEOs.
There's a Bible study happening in
Muthaiga.
Before you go for golf, you first of all
attend your Bible study.
UH THOSE PLACES ARE NOT FOR the wicked.
YOU CANNOT BE A GOVERNMENT AND YOU'RE
MEETING UNDER A TREE. IT IS ERROR.
YOU MUST MEET WHERE GOVERNMENTS MEET.
HALLELUJAH.
WE WANT TO DECLARE BECAUSE because they
THEY SAY THEIR WELLS ARE BEING RED DUG.
[music]
SOME OF US MAY NOT GO BACK TO UHURU
PARK, BUT THERE'S A GENERATION THAT
NEEDS TO GO BACK TO UHURU PARK. WE WANT
TO DECLARE
>> [music]
>> AGREEING HERE AS MEN OF PRAYER. We want
to declare the CITY IS OPENING [music]
UP AGAIN FOR MINISTRY AND THE GOSPEL. WE
DECLARE UHURU PARK IS OPEN FOR THE
DECLARATION OF THE WORD. WE DECLARE
KICC,
WE OPEN YOU IN THE SPIRIT FOR CASHERS,
[music] FOR CONFERENCES, FOR GATHERINGS,
FOR IMPARTATION. WE OPEN OTHER HALLS
THAT HAVE NOT YET BEEN OPENED. KENYA
CINEMA, NAIROBI CINEMA AND OTHER HALLS,
WE OPEN [music] THEM UP NOW. WE OPEN
BIBLE STUDIES. WE OPEN FELLOWSHIPS. WE
OPEN [music] PRAYER MEETINGS. WE OPEN
GATHERINGS OF MEN. WHEREVER MEN WILL
BEGIN TO GATHER, WE RECLAIM THE CITY FOR
JESUS. WE RECLAIM THE CITY FOR JESUS.
NAIROBI, HEAR THE WORD OF THE LORD. WE
RECLAIM YOU FOR JESUS. WE RECLAIM YOU
FOR JESUS. THE CASHERS ARE COMING BACK.
PRAYER WALKS ARE COMING BACK.
MINISTRIES, REVIVALS, OUTPOURINGS, THEY
ARE COMING BACK IN THE CITY AGAIN IN THE
NAME [music] OF JESUS.
AND NOW WE ANNOUNCE
>> [music]
>> EVERY gatekeeper
people that are planted in offices to
utter. Allow me to say what I'm seeing
in the spirit.
I'm seeing many fellowships in hotels.
That young people are meeting putting a
table round and they're beginning to
fellowship.
Because
this word has been very loud. The Josiah
No, no, the Josiah. Go and study it. The
Josiah revival.
The Josiah that a 16-year-old
could lead a revival. The Lord is saying
that is what is coming. You'll begin to
hear 16-year-olds,
17, 19, [music] 20 revealing mysteries.
THAT IS WHAT IS HAPPENING. ALLOW ME TO
TELL YOU YOU ARE NOT TOO YOUNG FOR
TRUTHS.
>> [music]
>> JUST BUY YOUR BIBLE AND TELL THE LORD,
OPEN IT UP FOR ME. YOU WILL BE
SURPRISED. GOD is not a respecter of
men. And let FEAR NOT GUIDE YOU.
LET US INTOXICATE TIKTOK. LET US
INTOXICATE TWITTER with revelations on
the word of God. Let the kingdom of our
God become the kingdom of this world.
DON'T BE AFRAID WHEREVER YOU ARE. 5
MINUTES YOU CAN DECIDE TO BE DOING A
10-MINUTES GOODNIGHT PRAYER EVERY
MIDNIGHT ON TIKTOK. [music] YOU WILL BE
SURPRISED HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE WAITING
FOR YOUR PRAYER. YOU CAN DECIDE TO DO A
VERSE A DAY AS A CHALLENGE ON TIKTOK.
YOU CAN DECIDE TO DO A CHAPTER A DAY
BECAUSE I BELIEVE IT IS A JOSIAH
REVIVAL. AND OUT OF THAT REVIVAL,
DANIELS WILL BE BORN. PEOPLE THAT HAVE
THE SYSTEM OF THE KINGDOM, YOU TAKE THEM
TO AMERICA, THEY ARE WORSHIPERS OF
YAHWEH. YOU TAKE THEM TO QATAR, THEY ARE
WORSHIPERS OF YAHWEH. YOU TAKE THEM TO
CHINA, THEY ARE WORSHIPERS OF YAHWEH.
WHEREVER YOU TAKE THEM, THEY ARE
ENTERING AS A SYSTEM. THEY CAN NEVER BOW
DOWN TO THE GODS OF THIS WORLD. THAT IS
THE GENERATION I'M THAT IS THE REVIVAL.
>> [music]
>> AND I DECLARE TO YOU, YOU are not here
by accident.
>> [music]
>> May you be that Josiah team.
That the systems of the kingdom will be
formed.
You know, when that system is formed,
conversation of Pastor is having sex
before marriage bad, the system will
confirm to you it is anti-system.
Because it is a kingdom system. It's a
culture.
OH, PASTOR
THE SYSTEM will confirm to you. This
system cannot FIT IN DUNDAR.
THE REASON IS MY DEBATE
WHEN YOU ROYAL PRIESTHOOD
WHEN YOU
YOUR SYSTEM
I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU YOU KNOW YOUR
SYSTEM IS GOING TO KNOW.
GOWN IS FUPI. YOU TELL ME MORNING SYSTEM
IS GOING TO TELL YOU SEE.
MY ANGEL WATCHING ON THESE TIES is going
to fly.
Your gown is going to BE LONG. TELL YOUR
NEIGHBOR NEIGHBOR. THE PROBLEM IS THE
SYSTEM.
AND YOU ARE GOING TO OPERATE NOW. I PRAY
THAT that system will be upon you in the
mighty name of Jesus. Before I hand
over, before I finish, if you are here
and you're not born again, that is the
entry of the system. We are not gathered
here because we are perfect men. We are
gathered here because there is a perfect
God that is perfecting our lives.
And we are still walking with that God.
If you're here and you're not born
again, lift up your hand. Our time is
well spent. I want to pray with you.
Our time is well spent.
Just ask your neighbor
Amen. Hallelujah. Thank you, my sister.
I see a hand over there.
I SEE ANOTHER HAND. I SEE OH MY GOD.
THANK YOU. TODAY TODAY TODAY IS THE DAY
OF SALVATION. SOMEBODY CELEBRATE THE
LORD.
THIS IS WHAT WE ARE GOING TO DO.
YOU MUST HAVE A NEIGHBOR. LET that
neighbor help them to the front.
>> [music]
>> CHURCH, WE CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT.
LET'S CELEBRATE. LET'S CELEBRATE.
>> [music]
>> HALLELUJAH.
HALLELUJAH.
>> [music]
[music]
>> LET'S CLAP FOR THEM. LET'S CLAP FOR
THEM.
>> [music]
>> MANY MORE COMING. DON'T STAY THERE. YOU
ARE A BACKSLIDER AND YOU'RE SAYING
PASTOR, I HAVE BEEN IN A CHURCH, BUT
[music] NOW I NEED TO BELONG TO THE
ECCLESIA. RUN to the altar. RUN TO THE
ALTAR. WE DIDN'T COME TO CONDEMN YOU. WE
CAME TO USHER YOU TO THE GOVERNMENT of
God. We came to usher YOU TO THE
GOVERNMENT OF GOD. RUN RUN RUN RUN.
DON'T BE AFRAID OF ANYONE.
DON'T BE AFRAID of anyone.
>> [music]
>> DON'T BE AFRAID OF ANYONE. CHURCH, LET
US CELEBRATE. GOD CAN ORGANIZE A meeting
[music]
just because of these people. GOD CAN
MAKE IT POSSIBLE JUST BECAUSE OF THESE
LOVED ONES.
>> [music]
>> I want you to say this prayer after me.
Say Lord Jesus,
I come into your presence.
>> [music]
>> I realize
that I am a sinner.
And today
I open up my heart
to receive you
as Lord
and savior
over my life.
Holy Spirit of God,
come into my life
and make me a new creation
in Jesus mighty name.
Let me pray for you. Heavenly Father,
thank you for these souls that have come
to you today in the name that above
every other name. Jehovah God, this is
the reason why we gathered here today.
>> [music]
>> I pray that Jehovah God, you will
sustain them in prayer. You will sustain
them in their walk with you in the name
of Jesus Christ. I decree that these
will become great evangelists of our
time. I decree they will become great
apostles of our time in the name that
above every other name. May the power of
the Holy Spirit, oh God, come upon them,
Heavenly Father, like it did Paul in the
name that above every other name, and he
was transformed into a new person in the
name that above every other name. And so
we decree and declare now, may your
destinies arise in Jesus mighty name.
For I bless you in the name of God the
Father, God the Son, and God the Holy
Spirit, and everybody shouted a big
amen.
>> [music]
>> What a
What apostle
Oh, may the Lord bless us. May the Lord
watch over us. May he cause his face to
shine upon us. May we go and possess the
gates of the enemy. [music]
May we reign in this nation. May the
government come to us for help in the
mighty name of Jesus I pray. Amen. Thank
you, sir.
I don't think there's anything.
>> [music]
>> Mine is just to say thank you to the
team led by Pastor Patrick and Patrick.
I just lift up your hand. Thank you for
convening this. Uh Pastor Evangelist
Kibali Stampede with your wife. Thank
you. I want to appreciate also Pastor
William who is part of the truth
mentorship and Pastor Ken Jogu. Wherever
Ken is, he's praying. It's because he's
a man of prayer. Where is he?
Oh, Ken. I know you're speaking in
tongues. Thank you, sir. Now you can say
amen. I also want to appreciate Pastor
Eugene. Thank you. These are we serve
together. Pastor Tamani, thank you. Uh
Elder Moji Shortbaba, we bless God for
you. May God bless you. We we we
Thank you. I also saw a man of God
there. Please, let me get Tell me your
name, sir, so that we can appreciate
you.
Yes.
Pastor
Pastor David, God bless you. God bless
you. Thank you for coming. And there is
Pastor
Robah, God bless you. Pastor Anita, may
God bless you.
The The available female pastor, Anita,
So, can you turn to your neighbor and
just tell them, "Neighbor,
from today,
you're not just a member of a church,
you're a member of a government.
Behave like so."
And now share the words of the grace.
And now the grace of our Lord Jesus
Christ and the love of God and the
fellowship of the Holy Spirit be with us
now and forever more. Amen. Surely,
goodness and mercy
all the days of our lives, and we shall
dwell in the house of the Lord forever
and ever. Amen. This one